(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-31T01:16:22.717728",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ooh～
Ooh~
just look around and see, it's so incredible!
so many smiles in a sea of light
take one step with me and you'll be dazzled,
there's magic in the air tonight
the hours zoom zoom zoom
my heart goes boom boom boom
the world is brighter because you believe in me
let's shout it loud loud loud
our time is right now
we're on the edge of destiny
for a moment, i can dream with you
every miracle we hoped for might come true
we come together, reaching out from far and wide,
and suddenly, you're here by my side!
when our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
together, we're all for one.
(let's sing! all for one!)
the thrill of happiness is all around us!
jump in, 'cause it's all for one
(let's sing! all for one!!)
we're on our way to good times, good vibes
we'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
hey!
all that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward,
we're singing, all for one!
all for one!
everything's in motion,
get up and start the celebration,
come see the wonders here beyond imagination
we're joining hands for the world to see (uh-huh)
We're joining hands for the world to see,
feel the love and the energy!
the hours zoom zoom zoom
my heart goes boom boom boom
a dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
let's shout it loud loud loud
our time is right now
we're here together, finally!
every moment takes my breath away;
there's a feeling here that words cannot convey,
we hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song,
and suddenly, our hearts beat as one!
every voice ringing loud and clear, so glad to be here
together, we're all for one.
(let's sing! all for one!)
we'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
jump in, 'cause it's all for one
(let's sing! all for one!)
keep up the hype, it's good times good vibes
remember this night the rest of our lives
hey!
raise up your hands and sway, your light will lead our way,
we're shining, all for one!
all for one!
so bring your memories, your joy and your hope,
we'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road, oh, oh
feel the music in your passionate soul,
we're here right now, so let the good times roll, oh, oh
every time that i'm with you,
i could swear it's like a wish is coming true
so i'll believe in you if you believe in me,
together we can chase all our dreams!
(1, 2, 3, 4, 5!)
when our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
together, we're all for one.
(let's sing! all for one!)
the thrill of happiness is all around us!
jump in, 'cause it's all for one
(let's sing! all for one!!)
we're on our way to good times, good vibes
we'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
hey!
all that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward,
we're singing, all for one!
all for one!
when our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
together, we're all for one.
(let's sing! all for one!)
the thrill of happiness is all around us!
jump in, 'cause it's all for one
(let's sing! all for one!!)
we're on our way to good times, good vibes
we'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
hey!
all that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward,
we're singing, all for one!
all for one!
Every order has a chance to get a rare version of the set! Pre-order today at hyte.com/allforone
WAH! Good Morning, Afternoon, and Evening! It's me Ina!
I hope everyone is excited for the concert! I know I am!
I've been AmiAmi's ambassador for a full year now, and it's been so much fun sharing all the great memories and the cool merch with you!
I've been using AmiAmi for a long time, but I still get excited every time I spot something WAHnderful on AmiAmi—it's like finding treasure!
Whenever you find cute merch of your oshi on AmiAmi, be sure to let us know, okay?
Let's give AmiAmi a big thank you for everything they've done this year! Everyone say, Thank you AmiAmi!
Anyways, let's make more amazing memories tonight! Make sure to cheer with everything you've got, okay?
WAH!
On the Run! hololive English -Advent- 2nd Anniversary Live
It's Ollie's holoplus Zom-Raid Time! Show your hype, share your thoughts, and ask Ollie about hololive production events in New York!
Official Hashtag #holoAllForOne hololive English 3rd Concert ALL.FOR.ONE
Attention For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
In-Stock Merch Essentials Pack (28 Types) ¥8,800 each
Just look around and see, it’s so incredible
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you’ll be dazzled
There’s magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom, zoom, zoom, my heart goes boom, boom, boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let’s shout it loud, loud, loud, our time is right now
We’re on the edge of destiny
For a moment, I can dream with you
Every miracle we hoped for might come true
We come together, reaching out from far and wide
And suddenly, you’re here by my side
When our voices and hearts unite, we’re gonna shine bright
Together, we’re all for one, all for one
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in, ’cause it’s all for one, all for one
We’re on our way to good times, good vibes
We’ll treasure this day the rest of our lives
All that we waited for, the dream we’re striving toward
We’re singing, all for one, all for one
Everything’s in motion, get up and start the celebration
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We’re joining hands for the world to see
Feel the love and the energy
The hours zoom, zoom, zoom, my heart goes boom, boom, boom
A dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let’s shout it loud, loud, loud, our time is right now
We’re here together, finally
Every moment takes my breath away
There’s a feeling here that words cannot convey
We hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song
And suddenly, our hearts beat as one
Every voice ringing loud and clear, so glad to be here
Together, we’re all for one, all for one
We’ll sing in harmony and we’ll be happy
Jump in, ’cause it’s all for one, all for one
Keep up the hype, it’s good times, good vibes
ooh～
Ooh...
just look around and see - it's so incredible !
Just look around and see—it's so incredible!
so many smiles in a sea of light
take one step with me and you'll be dazzled ,
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled,
there's magic in the air tonight
the hours zoom zoom zoom
my heart goes boom boom boom
the world is brighter because you believe in me
let's shout it loud loud loud
our time is right now
we're on the edge of destiny
for a moment , i can dream with you
For a moment, I can dream with you
every miracle we hoped for might come true
we come together , reaching out from far and wide ,
We come together, reaching out from far and wide,
and suddenly , you're here by my side !
And suddenly, you're here by my side!
when our voices and hearts unite , we're gonna shine bright !
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
together , we're all for one .
Together, we're all for one.
(let's sing ! all for one ! )
(Let's sing! All for one!)
the thrill of happiness is all around us !
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
jump in , 'cause it's all for one
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
(let's sing ! all for one ! ! )
(Let's sing! All for one!)
we're on our way to good times , good vibes
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
we'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
hey !
Hey!
all that we waited for , the dream we're striving toward ,
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward,
we're singing , all for one !
We're singing, all for one!
all for one !
All for one!
everything's in motion ,
Everything's in motion,
get up and start the celebration ,
Get up and start the celebration,
come see the wonders here beyond imagination
we're joining hands for the world to see ( uh - huh )
We're joining hands for the world to see (uh-huh)
feel the love and the energy !
Feel the love and the energy!
the hours zoom zoom zoom
my heart goes boom boom boom
a dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
let's shout it loud loud loud
our time is right now
we're here together , finally !
We're here together, finally!
every moment takes my breath away ;
Every moment takes my breath away;
there's a feeling here that words cannot convey ,
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey,
we hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song ,
We hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song,
and suddenly , our hearts beat as one !
And suddenly, our hearts beat as one!
every voice ringing loud and clear , so glad to be here
Every voice ringing loud and clear, so glad to be here
together , we're all for one .
Together, we're all for one.
(let's sing ! all for one ! )
(Let's sing! All for one!)
we'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
jump in , 'cause it's all for one
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
(let's sing ! all for one ! )
(Let's sing! All for one!)
keep up the hype , it's good times good vibes
Keep up the hype, it's good times good vibes
remember this night the rest of our lives
hey !
Hey!
raise up your hands and sway , your light will lead our way ,
Raise up your hands and sway, your light will lead our way,
we're shining , all for one !
We're shining, all for one!
all for one !
All for one!
so bring your memories , your joy and your hope ,
So bring your memories, your joy and your hope,
we'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road , oh , oh
We'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road, oh, oh
feel the music in your passionate soul ,
Feel the music in your passionate soul,
we're here right now , so let the good times roll , oh , oh
We're here right now, so let the good times roll, oh, oh
every time that i'm with you ,
Every time that I'm with you,
i could swear it's like a wish is coming true
so i'll believe in you if you believe in me ,
So I'll believe in you if you believe in me,
together we can chase all our dreams !
Together we can chase all our dreams!
( 1 , 2, 3 , 4 , 5 ! )
(1, 2, 3, 4, 5!)
when our voices and hearts unite , we're gonna shine bright !
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
together , we're all for one .
Together, we're all for one.
(let's sing ! all for one ! )
(Let's sing! All for one!)
the thrill of happiness is all around us !
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
jump in , 'cause it's all for one
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
(let's sing ! all for one ! ! )
(Let's sing! All for one!)
we're on our way to good times , good vibes
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
we'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
hey !
Hey!
all that we waited for , the dream we're striving toward ,
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward,
we're singing , all for one !
We're singing, all for one!
Yuh
Rise up!
Come in closer now!
Let's ride...
Bring it on!
Get down
Right now
Fighters
Yeah
We running the world
We're running the world
Fearless
Ow!
Step it up now!!
Oh we've got the power, unstoppable
The fire burning up inside our soul
Nothing brings us down, no matter what
We're gonna break through
Never stop! Gotta keep it going
On & on we go
on and on we go.
Crashing into the dark, yeah we gon' break the rules
Nobody can do what we can, no!!
Get up and move! Break all of the rules
Now, moving to the groove, keep it extra cool
We're extraordinary
Got em' all under our control
Ayo, back it up! Break it down!
Let us guide the way...
Louder, louder, to the beat!
Fly higher! Higher to the sky!
Hey now, we gon' vibe
Ain't no time to waste, yes!
Listen to your heart, then you'll find your way
Got lost inside reality
I heard a whisper calling me, calling me
I see it now we found ourselves
I see it now, we've found ourselves,
That's who we are...
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Start again
We're never gonna stop!!
光輝く stars, 導きあって ダンス
Radiant stars, guiding each other, let's dance.
Hey!
Start again, let go and let it flow!
Ready or not here we go!
Supernatural, 煌めく sparkling
Supernatural, sparkling bright,
無限に広がる stage
endless stage expanding,
響かせて now sing along!
make it resonate, now sing along!
Feel the rhythm taking over, keep it going On & on!!
Feel the rhythm taking over, keep it going on and on!
Shout out loud! And reach out to the moon
Not afraid, there's nothing left to lose!
A start of something more, yes! Turn it up!
Into the new world, we are unbreakable now!!
Hey now, what's goin on?
Let's take it real slow
From head to toe
So ready or not!
Level up to our heat 'Burning, burning, burning!!'
Focus
All eyes on me!
Step by step, funk it out!
Push it to the limit till the end!
Push it to the limit 'til the end!
Yeah yeah
Got lost inside reality
I heard a whisper calling me, calling me
I see it now we found ourselves
I see it now, we've found ourselves,
That's who we are...
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Start again
We're never gonna stop!!
光輝く stars, 導きあって ダンス
Radiant stars, guiding each other, let's dance.
Hey!
Start again, let go and let it flow!
Ready or not here we go!
Supernatural, 煌めく sparkling
Supernatural, sparkling bright,
無限に広がる stage
endless stage expanding,
響かせて now sing along!
make it resonate, now sing along!
Feel the rhythm taking over, keep it going On & on!!
Feel the rhythm taking over, keep it going on and on!
Shout out loud! And reach out to the moon
Not afraid, there's nothing left to lose!
A start of something more, yes! Turn it up!
Into the new world, we are unbreakable now!!
Hey now, what's goin on?
Let's take it real slow
From head to toe
So ready or not!
Level up to our heat 'Burning, burning, burning!!'
Focus
All eyes on me!
Step by step, funk it out!
Push it to the limit till the end!
Push it to the limit 'til the end!
Yeah yeah
Louder, louder, to the beat!
Fly higher! Higher to the sky!
Louder, louder, go louder, go louder
This is us for ruling the world
Start again, we're never gonna stop!!
光輝く stars, 導きあって ダンス
Radiant stars, guiding each other, let's dance.
Hey!
Start again, let go and let it flow!
Ready or not here we go!
Supernatural, 煌めく sparkling
Supernatural, sparkling bright,
無限に広がる stage
endless stage expanding,
響かせて now sing along!
make it resonate, now sing along!
Feel the rhythm taking over, keep it going On & on!!
Feel the rhythm taking over, keep it going on and on!
Shout out loud! And reach out to the moon
Not afraid, there's nothing left to lose!
A start of something more, yes! Turn it up!
Into the new world, we are unbreakable now!!
Shout out loud!
And reach out to the moon
Not afraid, there's nothing left to lose!
A start of something more, yes! Turn it up!
Into the new world, we are unbreakable now!!
We are unbreakable now!!
私のもの そう私のもの
Mine, yes, mine,
私のものでも
千の黄金 数百年の財宝 この船に眠る
a thousand golds, centuries of treasure sleeping on this ship.
続く夜の潮汐 そこに富が残る
The tide of night continues, where wealth remains.
海賊の夢があるのなら 頂くしかないでしょ？
If there's a pirate's dream, shouldn't we claim it?
「無謀な赤よ 若き盗人よ」
"Foolish red, young thief,"
「命をもっ て後悔に代えさせテヤロウ」
"pay for regret with your life."
止まない雨の弾丸で
With the bullets of ceaseless rain,
美しいほど この瞳 焦がす生命の炎
so beautiful, these eyes, the flame of life burning.
私のものでも 奪ってみろ
Mine, yes mine, try and take it.
命の証を 貴方の求める全てを
The proof of life, everything you desire.
輝きはくすんで 錆び付いて それでも 泥船にしがみつくなら 泡沫と共に 沈め
Radiance tarnishes and rusts, yet if you cling to a sinking ship, sink together with the bubbles.
こんなはずじゃないでしょ
This isn't how it was supposed to be, right?
無謀な火を焚き続けよ
Keep burning that reckless fire,
命燃えて後悔に曝すやろ やまない
burning life away, exposed to endless regrets—
雨の弾丸で
with bullets of rain.
薄氷程のこの日々を焦がす
Scorching these days like thin ice,
背中の羽の棘で全てを
with the thorns on the wings of my back,
細波に化かすやろ ほら奇麗なのだから
turning everything into ripples—look, because it's so beautiful.
わたしのもの わたしのもの
It's mine, it's mine,
奪って見せろ 命の証を
try and steal the proof of life!
あなたの求めるすべてを 輝かせて目眩くで
Shining and dazzling in everything you desire—
奪って見せろ 目ににしがみつくなら
try and steal it, if you're clinging to sight,
歌がたと共とに 沈め
sink together with the song.
君の日は凍り付いてる
Your days are frozen over,
極上の快楽の日を
on days of ultimate pleasure,
風は笑う
the wind laughs.
真っ直ぐの金銀珠玉 7つの水面を極曲に
Straight gold, silver, and jewels, reflecting seven water surfaces,
誓う一歩も 愚道と見を狙う
aiming even for a vow as a foolish path.
愚かなり身よ 思い出しなさい
How foolish you are, remember that!
探す無主の主を 怒りのようなその羽で
Searching for the masterless master, with wings like anger,
絶望の渦巻いて 二人の閉じた箱
swirling in despair, our closed box.
食べちゃおっか 諦めちゃおっか
Shall we eat it up? Shall we give up?
闇の中から逃げられるのもまだ束の間で
Escaping from darkness is still only for a moment,
欲望が重いから 撃ち落として
because desires are heavy, shoot them down!
わたしのもの わたしのもの
It's mine, it's mine,
自分自身を信じ込ましたスパッタ
convincing myself, spatter!
地ばりつけて立て 気づいてさ
Nail it to the ground and stand up, notice it!
悪魔の手口 とのよの怪奇
The devil's methods, the world's bizarre wonders—
目を塞いで あなたの開けの中から
close your eyes, from within your dawn,
連れ出す引き船を シュートして わたしのもの
towing you out, shoot it, it's mine!
呪いのボラを 突き放したとしたならもう
If you push away the curse's mullet, already
枯れない魂まで 何の憂い
until a soul that never withers, what sorrow?
悲劇なんて 笑い飛ばして
Laugh off tragedies like that,
取り込もう 余計に火傷を負って
let's take it in, getting even more burned.
誘惑を宿した船 日はわたしだけ残っていく
The ship harboring temptation, the sun remains only with me,
二人にはもういないから
because there's no longer two of us.
Come on New York! Are you ready to put your hands up?
Come on, New York! Are you ready?
I want to see all your hands and let's go!
Put your hands up! I wanna see all your hands! Let's go!
Put your hands up! Put your, put your hands up!
痛いにも得にもなく ググッ
Neither painful nor profitable, goo-goo!
手荷物少なむ イズ ズンズン
Luggage getting lighter, iz-zunzun!
目配り手話話 アネル ネル ネバ ナッ タイム スリーピー ヤ
Watching out, signing and talking, never not time sleepy ya!
ここどこ? まえ ここ ここ ここ ここ
Where is this? Front, here, here, here, here!
ダンシングダウン 燦々新感信号
Dancing down, brilliant new sensations and signals!
勘違い 尋ねよう はしょるどこどこ
Misunderstanding, let's ask, rushing where-where?
ああ 一番地 そろそろ ショッピング
Ah, first block, shopping soon!
去る者を追わさる パンパン ピッ パッ ピッ パプー
Don't chase those who leave, pam-pam pip-pap-pip-papoo!
Put your hands up! Put your, put your hands up!
欲しいものは ほら これだろ? さあ
What you want is right here, isn't it? Now,
さあ もっと もっと もっと もっと もっと!
come on, more, more, more, more, more!
のらないでんかえ やっぱっぽりで
Don't just ride along, as expected,
笑わないで 踊れば アイ アイ アイ オー！
don't laugh, if you dance, ai ai ai oh!
今度は開いて 止まって終わったの 心飛ばせ！
Open this time, stopped and ended, make your heart fly!
タイタイタイタイパーティー！
Tai, tai, tai, tai, party!
ウー・ア・ア・ア・ア！
Ooh-aah-aah-aah-aah!
希望は意外とんだ
Hope is surprisingly soaring!
ウー・ア・ア・ア・ア！
Ooh-aah-aah-aah-aah!
アイロニーことんぱんち
Irony, a heavy punch!
繋がってんだ
We're connected!
奇跡こんなんだ人生
Miracles are just part of life!
想い出いるサルヒトが
Remembering those who wander by,
教えてんだ 働いてんだ 元気なんだ
We're teaching, working, staying energetic!
休みの日 毎日傷々 昨日アランシータ
Days off covered in scratches, yesterday was all messed up.
死んだウィンピー ちゃんちゃんとうた心
A dead wimpy soul with a melodic heart.
人類抹殺
Eradicating humanity!
レトロパンク暴走
Retropunk running wild!
アモ三振 早々警官進行
Amo three strikes, police advancing quickly,
もう指々まで ワンツースリー オンラインオンライン探偵社
Up to our fingertips, one, two, three, online online detectives.
Okay, New York! You're gonna hate me for saying this.
Let's go vintage!
今日も死ぬほど苦しい水タイ
Dying of pain again today!
無名な才能抜け無菌で
Nameless talent left in a sterile room,
ホレワイ ホレウェー
Hore-wa-i, hore-wa-e-e!
Everyone, we're just getting started! So give me your energy!
Put your hands up, put your hands up!
ワクミもほら これだろうかな
Excitement too, look, is this it?
そうワンワンワンワンワンワン
That's right, one, one, one...
ERROR! Error fix error!
ノライ全開へ早く
Full throttle, hurry!
笑わないで踊れ毎日
Don't laugh, dance every single day!
何度生きないでどうやっていの
How many times without living, how do you do it?
ほらいつも場で タイタイタイタイパーティー！
Look, always in the place, tai, tai, tai, party!
希望は意外とんだ
Hope is surprisingly soaring!
アイロニーことんぱんち 繋がってんだ
Irony, a heavy punch, we're connected!
Put your hands up, put your hands up!
New York! Are you ready for some spice?
Oh no, fell into the abyss unknown, left me bleeding heartless, all alone.
Yeah, yeah, no control, yeah, yeah.
Don't you dare apologize, turn my pocket, felt a cold knife, listen up cause here's some advice.
Yeah, out of time, way out of line.
It's taking over like a renegade, eye for an eye, I'll make you cry.
Tearing it down to just what I want now, keep calling me us at night.
You think so? Ready, ready, ready, yeah! Got me twisted, ready, ready, ready, yeah!
Taking the crown now you're calling me king, you're gonna hear us all sing.
Ready, ready, ready, yeah! Not a lifetime, ready, ready, ready, yeah!
Don't fuck it up, don't fuck it up, keep that aim, I got a boss that'll drive you insane.
Come over if you like, we'll have a lot of fun, but I got a lot of bite.
I do what I want, make sure you don't forget it, an army on my back saying, 'Sik, I'm just aesthetic!'
Not living in a line, we're right in the line, I wanna see the way you bleed.
It's taking over like a renegade, eye for an eye, I'll make you cry.
Tearing it down to just what I want now, keep calling me us at night.
You think so? Ready, ready, ready, yeah! Got me twisted, ready, ready, ready, yeah!
Taking the crown now you're calling me king, you're gonna hear us all sing.
Ready, ready, ready, yeah! Not a lifetime, ready, ready, ready, yeah!
Don't fuck it up, don't fuck it up, keep that aim, I got a boss that'll drive you insane.
I want it all, so give me some more, flames burn me up down into my core.
Oh, you wish that'd stay down, but then I just rise.
You're not my enemy, baby, you're dead to me! Hear my voice as it's screaming out loud, no doubt, yeah!
ooh, ah
la, la-la, la-la-la-la-la-la
la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
(K-I-R-A)
oh no
Fell into the abyss unknown,
left me bleeding, heartless, all alone, ayo, eyo
no control, ayo, eyo
Don't you dare apologize,
turn my back and felt a cold knife.
Listen up, 'cause here's some advice,
you're out of time, way out of line.
It's taking over like a renegade,
eye for an eye, I'll make you cry.
Tearing it down, do just what I wanna,
keep calling me a sinner.
Chim-ery-ery-era,
chim-ery-ery-era.
Taking the crown, now you're calling me king,
you gonna hear 'em all sing.
Chim-ery-ery-era, chim-ery-ery-era.
hololive English 3rd Concert ALL FOR ONE
Wait a minute, I'm cheating! Oh, Calli!
You're cheating, Calli?
Wait, didn't you know?
Oh, yeah.
Wait, we're not doing anything wrong.
We're not, we're not doing anything wrong.
No, no, no, we were just hugging as friends.
It was just tsk, tsk, tsk. Yes, right?
Yeah.
Okay! Kikkeriki!
Okay, let's introduce ourselves, yeah?
Hi!
Yes!
You start with the cheater. Oh, no, the cheater.
You also cheater?
Okay.
Go ahead! Hi! Kikkeriki!
I wish I was someone else right now,
but I'm Takanashi Kiara from hololive English Myth! Yay!
And you? It's IRyS from hololive English Promise.
Can I get a high-riiiiise?
Let's go!
We just performed a really high performance
of Chimera!
This is not my first time performing with you on your song.
Yeah, they put us together a lot these days.
Kind of a trend.
It is.
Kiara is a trend.
I'm sure they can't get enough of us, right?
Yeah, no, of course they can.
That's why we're here now too.
We're spice.
Yeah, we're sexy.
Oh, yes, we are. Yes, we are.
Of course we are.
Well, you know, this is the first MC.
That's right.
Which means
Oh? Oh?
We're going to do the sad news, right?
Yes.
But I want to deliver the sad news.
It's our first time, so I want to do it too.
I want to do it.
Well, in that case, we battle it out.
We're battling it out!
In front of all these people?
Yeah, there's no problem.
It's going to be, they're going to cheer for us.
So, we think of battles. What do we think about?
I think like recently a lot of the EN members
have been like doing arm wrestling.
Yeah. And I'm very well known for being a noodle arm person.
What about you?
I am very strong.
Everyone knows that IRyS is very strong.
Yeah. You are.
Well, you know, I usually am left-handed,
but I will use my right hand to give you a chance.
Okay?
Thank you, Senpai.
Okay, okay, okay.
And we'll take that. Shall we do it right now?
Let's go!
Okay. Come here.
Come here, come here.
Okay. Ready?
Count us down.
Okay.
Three, two, one, go!
Oh! Oh!
Ah! Ah!
Ah! I go win!
Yes!
I just beat it with my non-dominant arm.
Yeah, that was my right hand, though.
My left hand is my dominant arm, so that wasn't completely fair.
Let's do another game.
Another game?
Yes!
I mean, yeah, that's true, it wasn't fair.
In that case, what do you have in mind?
There's this game called, uh,
like blue right, blue light, red light,
not blue light.
That's red light, green light.
Red light, green light.
Okay.
Okay, then you perhaps stand on that side,
and I go towards you.
Okay.
Gotcha.
Okay, then I, I can win this.
I will get you.
I will get you, okay?
Okay.
Red light.
Oh, oh, green light.
Oh, sorry. Yeah, I was We're starting, we're starting.
Okay, okay. Red light!
Green light!
Red light, green light!
Red light!
Green light!
Red light! Green light! Red light! Green light!
Red light! Green light!
Not my blood! Not my blood!
Okay! Yay!
But that means it's a draw.
A draw? Which means
We get to say it together!
Ti-Ti-EN-EN.
It's not like this was scripted or anything. I swear our actions...
No, no, no, no.
The only thing that was scripted was our entrance.
Oh, yeah, that.
Okay. Um.
Then? Let's do it!
Let's do this, okay? Everybody...
watching on YouTube, mm-hm.
Are you aware that if you don't have a ticket, you might not be able to watch anymore of this?
What? Yes, guys!
This is the last of the free part on YouTube! If you want to watch more...
Yes, you have to buy... The streaming tickets are available in the description and official website!
Probably down there, yeah.
You can go get a streaming ticket.
Yeah, you would be crying like me until you buy them!
Yes! Do what she says, I recommend it.
Once you buy them you'll be happy and you'll be able to watch the rest of the concert.
Yes, yes! They're saying it too!
Yeah! Buy it! Buy it!
Besides that, one more thing...
Now that you got your tickets and you're ready to take even more screenshots, make sure to share them and your thoughts on social media using the hashtag #HoloAllForOne!
Yes! Yes, oh!
Yes. Oh, I think we should also...
Speaking of HoloAllForOne, I think it's time for us to...
you know, say the thing. Yeah, the thing.
You guys are all aware by now, right? But because of yesterday, it's called...
All for One. We say it together. We say it together, yeah? All of us.
All of us. Only you guys must...
Are you in or what? Okay.
All for one! All for one! Okay, okay.
Ready? Okay.
Free, two, one...
All for one! Woo!
ooh ~
just look around and see-it 's so incredible !
so many smiles in a sea of light
take one step with me and you'll be dazzled ,
there 's magic in the air tonight
the hours zoom zoom zoom
my heart goes boom boom boom
the world is brighter because you believe in me
let 's shout it loud loud loud
our time is right now
we 're on the edge of destiny
for a moment , i can dream with you
every miracle we hoped for might come true
we come together , reaching out from far and wide ,
and suddenly , you 're here by my side !
when our voices and hearts unite , we 're gonna shine bright !
together , we 're all for one .
(let 's sing ! all for one ! )
the thrill of happiness is all around us !
jump in , ’ cause it 's all for one
(let 's sing ! all for one ! ! )
we 're on our way to good times , good vibes
we 'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
hey !
all that we waited for , the dream we 're striving toward ,
we 're singing , all for one !
all for one !
Just look around and see-it's so incredible!
Just look around and see—it's so incredible!
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled,
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom, zoom, zoom, my heart goes boom, boom, boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud, loud, loud, our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment, I can dream with you
Every miracle we hoped for might come true
We come together, reaching out from far and wide,
And suddenly, you're here by my side!
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
Together, we're all for one.
(let's sing! all for one!)
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
(let's sing! all for one!!)
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey!
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward,
We're singing, all for one!
All for one!
Everything's in motion,
Get up and start the celebration,
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We're joining hands for the world to see
(uh-huh)
Feel the love and the energy!
The hours zoom, zoom, zoom, my heart goes boom, boom, boom
A dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud, loud, loud, our time is right now
We're here together, finally!
Every moment takes my breath away;
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey,
We hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song,
And suddenly, our hearts beat as one!
Every voice ringing loud and clear, so glad to be here
Together, we're all for one.
(let's sing! all for one!)
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
(let's sing! all for one!)
Keep up the hype, it's good times, good vibes
Remember this night the rest of our lives
Hey!
Raise up your hands and sway, your light will lead our way,
We're shining, all for one!
All for one!